<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_barmen_greeting_1">
		<text>Come on over, sis! I've got all the shit you're ever gonna need.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pas_b400_zulus_about_cover_1">
		<text>Keep moving, sis! I've got your back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pas_b400_zulus_about_cover_1">
		<text>Keep moving, sis! I've got your back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pas_b400_zulus_about_gates">
		<text>Press the button, sis!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pas_b400_zulus_about_train_gates_1">
		<text>Well, sis... let's rock and roll!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pas_b400_zulus_come_back_1">
		<text>Keep up, sis! We've got to keep moving forward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pas_b400_zulus_wait_for_me_1">
		<text>Come back, sis! We don't need a scout on this mission.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cc_generic-freedom-meet_hello_3">
		<text>What's up, sis?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cc_generic-killer-meet_hello_2">
		<text>Hey, sis!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cc_generic-stalker-meet_hello_2">
		<text>Hey, sis!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_quests_dialog_freedom_44">
		<text>Sis, if I knew I'd have gone there a long time ago. Getting away from Duty, the jar-heads and all this fighting would be worth it...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_arena_manager_start_51">
		<text>Sorry, sis, but you lose. Come again next time if you want.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_jup_1">
		<text>Nice to meet you, sis. Name's Garry, and I'm a guide - I usually roam around the centre of the Zone. I can take you to the Bar, Pripyat, the Red Forest, Zaton and the Jupiter Underground.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lukash_living_legend_finish_5">
		<text>Really? Well, the Zone's making us happy, so it worked anyway. Hell, I can already imagine the government fuming when we publish everything. Great job, sis. You deserve a medal, and this.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lazarus_greeting_0">
		<text>What's up, sis?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_do_not_know_1">
		<text>Sis, if I had all the answers, I wouldn't be in this shit dump.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_help_2">
		<text>Help me out, sis... Oh, God, it hurts!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_help_4">
		<text>Sis... Sis, save me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_help_16">
		<text>Hey, sis, can you share your first aid kit?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_information_350">
		<text>There's just nothing like the Zone, sis. Have you ever just seen the sky after an emission... the feeling of cool wind and a peace in the air... shit, I could write some poetry on that.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_information_363">
		<text>How about this for a story, sis: I was in the Red Forest because a friend of mine who had just quit the Zone left me coordinates for a stash of all his artefact-finding gear. I'm no blockhead, so I'm taking it real slow, observing first and then sneaking along. MY PDA led me up to a big tree; I walked around it and found my friend's pack in a huge fissure that ran down the trunk. I was just about to leave when I heard footsteps from the other side of the tree. I thought there were maybe five or six guys and they stopped moving for awhile so I snuck a peak around the side: a fucking squad of Monolith! So I just crouched there, behind the tree with half my body in the fissure. They didn't talk, but they did this weird sort of humming thing. Meanwhile, I'm thinking that it's all over for me; that they would notice me any second. I waited for six hours like that - imagine that! Then they left, and I hurried my lucky ass home.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_information_376">
		<text>Sis, just keep an eye out for new recruits doing anything fishy. Lukash says that Duty's trying to infiltrate us these days. Duty! Can you imagine some stuck-up army pissant trying to pass himself off as Freedom? Anyway, be on the lookout.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_information_391">
		<text>Hey sis, do you know Hawaiian? He told me to ask Free Stalkers if you knew about some guy named Degtyarev. Yeah, I don't know. Told him I'd do him a solid.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_information_482">
		<text>Hey sis, got any of the good stuff on you? Where's Yarik? He owes me three bottles of vodka and no, I wasn't too drunk to remember.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_task_1_about">
		<text>I need some help, sis. A Dutier brought me in his rifle for repairs but I messed it up pretty bad. I need to find a replacement for him before he comes to pick it up.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Hey, great! You found one. Thanks sis, you saved my ass.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_task_2_about">
		<text>Hey sis, can you do something for me? I gotta go somewhere but I heard there are mutants on the road leading out of the Bar. I'm no good at shooting, my aim is all shaky for some reason. Could you clear them out for me? I have a rifle that a customer never picked up that I can give you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_bar_visitors_stalker_mechanic_task_2_finish">
		<text>Thanks sis. Here's the rifle I promised you. Hope you have better luck than its previous owner... poor guy. Good thing he paid me in advance, hehe.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_17_fetch_finish">
		<text>Maximum respect, sis! Hold on to this artefact.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_jup_a6_freedom_leader_task_2_finish">
		<text>Well done! Now we can begin our invasion! Well, not now, later today... maybe tomorrow. Anyway, thanks sis.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_jup_a6_freedom_leader_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Ah, perfect. Good job sis.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_cont_mech_bandit_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Well, fuck me sideways! What a rarity... a real rarity. I'll give you another discount, you deserve it. Thanks, sis.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_finish">
		<text>Awesome sis! Thanks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trucks_cemetery_bandit_mechanic_task_1_about">
		<text>Sis, more than half of the stuff we got here is breaking apart, and I really need some tools to help out the lads. Wanna help?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trucks_cemetery_bandit_mechanic_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>Sis, more than half of the stuff we got here is breaking apart, and I really need some tools to help out the lads. Wanna help?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="devushka_help1_1">
		<text>Yes. Can't blame her. After you watch some of your friends get zombified before your eyes, makes sense you'd want to get the hell away from the place it happened. Between that, and having to fight Duty...eh. But she seems resolved to make the trip now. The two of you will be going to Yanov station in Jupiter. Drop these meds off with Loki once you arrive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="devushka_5_help_0">
		<text>Hey Lukash, a friend of mine wanted to come see you. I think you know her.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="pas_b400_zulus_no_meet_1">
		<text>No time for banter, sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_mechanic_st_0">
		<text>Share your story, sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_jup_depo_start_0">
		<text>Salutations, sister. My duty is to provide technical support for our brethren in the area.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_eidolon_start_0">
		<text>Praise the Monolith, sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_kbo_start_0">
		<text>Greetings, sister. I carry out Its will by preserving the equipment of our brotherhood.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_greh_trader_start_dialog_0">
		<text>Come, sister. I'll make sure you can serve the Zone well.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="red_greh_tech_st_1">
		<text>I'm forever but a humble servant. You know, sister, I used to work as an engineer for the Masters even before the Zone was created. I was one of the many who assembled the venerable Generators, with no authority to speak of, and a small, but important role to play in the Zone's creation. When the Masters ascended to Vyraj and our Father, Chernobog, was let loose to carry out their will, he recruited me into the ranks of newborn Sin in recognition of my part in the mission and mechanical skills. Nowadays, I toil constantly to maintain the equipment of our crusaders in satisfactory condition, so that they can carry out the will of Masters as well.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_game_start_dialog_1_1">
		<text>There is much work to be done, my sister. The Zone must be purged of the infidels. We must keep control of the mutant population. Your brothers need food and weapons. You will report to your Monolith elders, and we will give you your assignments. You must do your part. Praise Monolith and may the Monolith bless you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_hello_1">
		<text>Hello, sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_information_84">
		<text>Sister, should you ever be captured by an infidel, see to it that you give your life before you give a word. The secrecy and protection of the Monolith is imperative. All else is secondary.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_information_85">
		<text>Pray with me sister! 
		\n\nBlessed is the man who walks not on the paths of the infidel, nor stands in the way of the sinner. But his delight is the glory of the Monolith alone, and his glory he contemplates day and night. He is like a cliff, planted in streams of water, a stronghold of faith. The infidels are not so, they are like chaff that the wind drives away. Therefore the infidel will not stand before you; no sinner will be in the congregation of your glory. For our Monolith knows the way of the righteous, but the ways of the infidel will perish.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dyn_news_companion_life_monolith_1">
		<text>Sister, show no mercy to those who stand against the Monolith's will.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dyn_news_companion_life_monolith_7">
		<text>Be careful sister, the enemy may show up at any moment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_5_about">
		<text>I must be strong to serve the Monolith well but I confess my strength is weakening. Can you help me, sister?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_5_fetch_about">
		<text>My sister, I am very ill. Cleric has graciously offered to pray for me but I'm pretty sure I just need %ss. Please bring me some.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_5_fetch_finish">
		<text>Thank you my sister. May the glory of the Monolith shine upon you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_19_about">
		<text>Hello sister, want to kill some bastards? You give me their sweet little patches, and I'll give you an artefact. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_19_fetch_about">
		<text>Hello sister, want to kill some bastards? You give me their sweet little patches, and I'll give you an artefact. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_19_fetch_finish">
		<text>Thank you, sister, friend and helper. Here's your artefact.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_30_about">
		<text>Yes, help me, sister! Some bastard has put a price on my head. Take care of him for me, and I will pay you double the bounty he has on me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_34_about">
		<text>My sister, Rabbit has asked of me that I slay one of the infidels for the good of the Monolith. I fear I have failed him, as I was not able to get to the target. Will you not complete my task and redeem my failure?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_36_about">
		<text>My sister, we have sighted the enemy in the area. We are going to alert our brothers to do battle. Go there now. Destroy them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_36_finish">
		<text>You have done well, my sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_43_finish">
		<text>You have done well, my sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_63_about">
		<text>Sister, we shall slay the brazen infidel for the good of the Monolith and our cause. Are you willing to help?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_64_about">
		<text>My sister, we have sighted the enemy in the area. We are going to alert our brothers to prepare for battle. Go there now. The infidels must be purified.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_64_finish">
		<text>You have done well, my sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_65_about">
		<text>The mutant population in the area is growing unstable, sister. We must cull their numbers to maintain balance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_65_finish">
		<text>You have done well, my sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_jup_depo_task_3_about">
		<text>We will be able to surpass them all, sister! To accomplish that, I require tools for calibrating our weapons. Please, locate a set and bring it to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_jup_depo_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>We will be able to surpass them all, sister! To accomplish that, I require tools for calibrating our weapons. Please, locate a set and bring it to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_trader_monolith_kbo_task_2_about">
		<text>I have an important mission for you, sister. We have sent a squad of our scouts to observe unusual activities in the area. A day has passed and they are nowhere to be found. Their failure has brought shame on us all! It is up to us to see if they can still be redeemed. Here, this is the PDA signal frequency for one of the scouts. Trace it and discover what happened to them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_trader_monolith_kbo_task_2_finish">
		<text>This information will be useful. Thank you, sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_eidolon_task_1_about">
		<text>We are besieged. Infidels wish to exploit the almighty Monolith. Driven by avarice. Ignorance. Base desires. On behalf of the Monolith. We act, the guardians. Purge the infidels. Collect their badges. As a trophy. A sign of our unquestionable, superiority. Go, sister. Destroy them all.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_eidolon_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>We are besieged. Infidels wish to exploit the almighty Monolith. Driven by avarice. Ignorance. Base desires. On behalf of the Monolith. We act, the guardians. Purge the infidels. Collect their badges. As a trophy. A sign of our unquestionable, superiority. Go, sister. Destroy them all. Acquire %s on your mission.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_eidolon_task_1_about">
		<text>We are besieged. Infidels wish to exploit the almighty Monolith. Driven by avarice. Ignorance. Base desires. On behalf of the Monolith. We act, the guardians. Purge the infidels. Collect their badges. As a trophy. A sign of our unquestionable, superiority. Go, sister. Destroy them all.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_eidolon_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>We are besieged. Infidels wish to exploit the almighty Monolith. Driven by avarice. Ignorance. Base desires. On behalf of the Monolith. We act, the guardians. Purge the infidels. Collect their badges. As a trophy. A sign of our unquestionable, superiority. Go, sister. Destroy them all. Acquire %s on your mission.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_eidolon_task_3_about">
		<text>We protect the Monolith. The Monolith protects us. We serve, and the Zone delivers. Splendid fruit, resplendent with its unequalled brilliance. Powerful, to empower us. Go now, harvest the fruit, sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_eidolon_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>We protect the Monolith. The Monolith protects us. We serve, and the Zone delivers. Splendid fruit, resplendent with its unequalled brilliance. Powerful, to empower us. Go now, harvest the fruit, sister. Harvest a "%s" artefact, to bolster our strength.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_eidolon_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Excellent. Marvellous. A sight to behold. You have got my gratitude, loyal sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lider_monolith_haron_task_1_about">
		<text>My sister, your help is needed in the destruction of the infidels.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lider_monolith_haron_task_1_finish">
		<text>Blessings of the Monolith upon you, sister! Take what you deserve.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lider_monolith_haron_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Outstanding, sister. This is for you, from the Monolith.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="mechanic_monolith_kbo_task_1_about">
		<text>I need your help, sister. I require tools for our equipment so that our brethren may spread the word of the Monolith more effectively.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_kbo_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>I need your help, sister. I require tools for our equipment so that our brethren may spread the word of the Monolith more effectively.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_kbo_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Excellent work, sister. Everything we gain from future improvements will go to our charity, and your contribution will grant you a small discount.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_kbo_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Excellent work, sister. Everything we gain from future improvements will go to our charity, and your contribution will grant you an additional discount.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_kbo_task_3_about">
		<text>The last set of tools that you brought here was... adequate, but why stop at what has been achieved when we can attain something even better? What we need are the best tools in the Zone. I ask of you to serve Its will one last time, my sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_kbo_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>The last set of tools that you brought here was... adequate, but why stop at what has been achieved when we can attain something even better? What we need are the best tools in the Zone. I ask of you to serve Its will one last time, my sister.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_monolith_kbo_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Outstanding work, sister. Rest assured, I will mention your contribution to our brothers... and I promise to provide any assistance within my ability.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_red_greh_trader_task_1_about">
		<text>As the true keepers of the Zone, we must act fast and keep its secrets hidden away from the eyes of this sinning world. One of the many secrets can be found inside the laboratory known as "X-16". Bring them to me, sister. We will keep them safe.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_red_greh_trader_task_2_msg_join">
		<text>Thank you, sister. I'm truly thankful... Lead the way, it is time to leave this old world behind.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_red_greh_trader_task_4_about">
		<text>Time has come, sister. The monolith elders are seeking our help to purge Limansk and defeat the enemies lurking inside. Make us proud.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_red_greh_tech_task_1_about">
		<text>As the true keepers of the Zone, we must act fast and keep its secrets hidden away from the eyes of this sinning world. One of the many secrets can be found inside the laboratory known as "X-18". Bring them to me, sister. We will keep them safe.</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>